Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art registrar's office records, 1869-2013 COR0005.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Deaccession files, 1944-2013; Series 16
  - Deaccessions general file, 1960-2013; Series 16 subseries 2
    - Morris, William (2 prints) 1998.52.12, .18, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 24)
    - Priou, Louis - Family of Satyrs 74.21, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 25)
    - Richards, Wm. Trost - On the Coast of New England 97.12, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 26)
    - Robinson, Theodore - Boats in a Harbor 66.35, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 27)
    - Sartain, William - Arab Camp, Algiers 41.57, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 28)
    - Sawyer, Wells M. - Winter at Snug Rock 40.20, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 29)
    - Smith - Snow Goose 1998.52.5, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 30)
    - Stuart, GIlbert - John Stevens Ellery 1980.100, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 31)
    - Stuart, Gilbert - John Stevens Ellery Provenance/Biography, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 32)
    - Stuart, Gilbert - John Stevens Ellery Exh. History/References, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 33)
    - Tarbell, Edmund Charles - Still Life 41.23, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 34)
    - Twachtman, John Henry - Spring Landscape 41.26, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 35)
    - Clark? Settee (chest) Inlaid 37.72, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 36)
    - Unknown, Late Empire Settee, mahogany 48.9, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 37)
    - Waugh, Frederick - The Open Sea 64.21.5, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 38)
    - West, Benjamin - Cupid & Psyche 10.1, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 39)
    - Wilson - Ruddy Duck 1998.52.16, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 40)
    - Wyant, Alexander Helwig - Late Afternoon Landscape 67.16, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 41)
    - Wyant, Alexander H. - Early Autumn, Adirondacks 38.5, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 42)
    - Yewell, George Henry - Young Boy 66.27, circa 2010; Series 16 subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 43)
- Collections management files, 1923-2003; Series 17
  - Collections management policy project files, 1990-2003; Series 17 subseries 1
    - Acquisition of artwork totals, 1990-1998; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Donor list, 1997; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Acquisition totals, 1999-2000; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folders 3-4)
    - Collections Management Policy Project - background, 1997-1998; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Collections Management Project - exhibitions (research for parts of CMP), 1997-1998; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Collections Management Policy Project - draft for discussion, 1997-1998; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Collections Management Policy Project - notes on meetings with staff, 1997-1998; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Collections Management Policy Project - memos/outlines, 1997-1998; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Collections Management Policy Project - materials received from other museums, 1997-1998; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Collections Management Policy Project - materials received from staff, 1997-1998; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - AAM Self Study, 1997; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - PDS Inventory, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folders 13-16)
    - PDS Inventory: Muybridge, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 1, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 2, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 3, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 4, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 5, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 6, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 7, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 8, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 9, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 10, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 11, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 12, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 26)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 13/OLGA, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 27)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 14, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 28)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 15, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 29)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 16, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 30)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 17, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 31)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 18, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 32)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 19, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 33)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 20, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 34)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 21, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 35)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 22, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 36)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 23, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 37)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 24, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 38)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 25, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 39)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 26, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 40)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 27, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 41)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 28, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 42)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 29, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 43)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 30, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 44)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 31, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 45)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 32, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 46)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 33, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 47)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 34, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 48)
    - PDS Inventory: Rack 35/OLGA, 2003; Series 17 subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 49)
  - Assistant Registrar files, 1997-2003; Series 17 subseries 2
  - Object files, 1923-1997; Series 17 subseries 3